Guide to the Guerrilla TV Archive 1965-1997 MSS 138 MSS.138
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII: Audio Recordings, 55163
  - Subseries A: Guerrilla TV Interviews, 55211
    - Skip Sweeney, San Francisco, Video Free America and "My Father Sold Studebakers" Part 2 of 3, 10/2/1983; 138.0130; 55239 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0130, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0130)
    - Skip Sweeney, San Francisco, Video Free America. Part 3 of 3, 10/2/1983; 138.0131; 55238 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0131, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0131)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 61 min.
    - Parry Teasdale and Carol Vontobel, Phoenicia NY, discussing Videofreex and Lanesville TV. Part 1 of 2, 4/18/1984; 138.0132; 55237 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0132, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0132)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell UD90, 93 min.
    - Parry Teasdale and Carol Vontobel, Phoenicia NY, discussing Videofreex and Lanesville TV. Part 2 of 2, 4/18/1984; 138.0133; 55236 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0133, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0133)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell UD90, 94 min.
    - Rick Tejado-Flores, Los Angeles, 10/5/1983; 138.0134; 55235 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0134, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0134)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 67 min.
    - Mary Tiseo, Boston, discusses Urban Planning Aid, 11/11/1983; 138.0135; 55234 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0135, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0135)
    - TVTV "The Good Times Are Killing Me.", undated; 138.0136; 55233 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0136, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0136)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, 60 min.
    - "TVTV at the Superbowl.", undated; 138.0137; 55232 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0137, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0137)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, 39 min.
    - Eric Trigg and Howard Wise, EAI Video Art, 11/27/1981; 138.0138; 55231 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0138, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0138)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, 58 min.
    - Arthur Tsuchiya, discusses Visual Studies Workshop (VSW), Ithaca Film and Video Art, 6/1981; 138.0139; 55230 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0139, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0139)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Realistic Supertape Cassette C-60, 66 min.
      Preservation note: "Content comes from phone interviews and answering machines some gaps between content, and a great deal of electrical interference/artifacting inherent in the source"
    - Keiko Tsuno, Part 1 of 2, 5/8/1984; 138.0140; 55229 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0140, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0140)
    - Keiko Tsuno, Part 2 of 2, 5/8/1984; 138.0141; 55228 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0141, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0141)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, 34 min.
    - Edin Velez, New York, giving a lecture to Fordham students on his work. Part 1 of 2, 3/1983; 138.0142; 55227 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0142, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0142)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, 63 min.
    - Edin Velez, New York, giving a lecture to Fordham students on his work. Part 2 of 2, 3/1983; 138.0143; 55226 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0143, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0143)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, 54 min.
    - Bill Viola, Part 1 of 3, 10/18/1982; 138.0144; 55225 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0144, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0144)
    - Bill Viola, Part 2 of 3, 10/18/1982; 138.0145; 55224 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0145, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0145)
    - Bill Viola, Part 3 of 3, 10/18/1982; 138.0146; 55223 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0146, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0146)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, 16 min.
    - Bill Viola, 11/1987; 138.0147; 55222 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0147, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0147)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Denon HD8-90, 94 min.
    - Ann Volkes, Part 1 of 2, 4/25/1984; 138.0148; 55221 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0148, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0148)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Scotch C-90, 92 min.
    - Ann Volkes, Part 2 of 2, 4/25/1984; 138.0149; 55220 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0149, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0149)
    - Gail Waldron, Minneapolis, discusses BAVC and "The Life and Times of Rose Maddox", 6/11/1983; 138.0150; 55219 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0150, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0150)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK SA90, 57 min.
    - Burwell Ware and Eddie Kurtz, New Orleans, discusses NOVAC. Part 1 of 2, 1/31/1984; 138.0151; 55218 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0151, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0151)
    - Burwell Ware and Eddie Kurtz, New Orleans, discusses NOVAC. Part 2 of 2, 1/31/1984; 138.0152; 55217 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0152, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0152)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 84 min.
    - Morrie Warshowski, San Francisco, discusses BAVC present and future, comments on Northwest video, 9/29/1983; 138.0153; 55216 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0153, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0153)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 47 min.
    - Don West, Part 1 of 2, 5/21/1984; 138.0154; 55215 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0154, E-records fales_mss138)
    - Don West, Part 2 of 2, 5/21/1984; 138.0155; 55214 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0155, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0155)
    - Megan Williams, Los Angeles, TVTV, 10/18/1983; 138.0156; 55213 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0156, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0156)
    - Ann Woodward, 4/10/1984; 138.0157; 55212 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0157, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0157)
      Original Format: 1/4" Audiocassette, Maxell UD90, 95 min.
  - Subseries B: Conferences, 55179
    - American Film Institute (AFI) "Role of the Subject" participants include Blumberg, Costello and Studs Terkel, June 11, 1982. Part 1 of 2, 138.0158; 55210 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0158, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0158)
      Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, 61 min.
    - AFI "Role of the Subject" participants include Blumberg, Costello and Studs Terkel, June 11, 1982. Part 2 of 2, 138.0159; 55209 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0159, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0159)
      Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, 5 min.
    - Association of Independent Video and Filmmakers (AIVF) "Docs to Drama" October 28, 1987. Part 1 of 2, 138.0160; 55208 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0160, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0160)
      Audiocassette, unmarked, 94 min.
    - AIVF "Docs to Drama" October 28, 1987. Part 2 of 2, 138.0161; 55207 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0161, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0161)
      Audiocassette, unmarked, 30 min.
    - American Library Association (ALA) "Video:An Alternative Information Service" June 1980. Part 1 of 2, 138.0162; 55206 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0162, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0162)
      Audiocassette, unmarked, 63 min.
      Preservation note: "Tape incubated and housed in new cartridge; old label: '99th Annual ALA Conference 80107-071 VIDEO: AN ALTERNATIVE INFORMATION SERVICE New York City, N.Y. June 1980 AMERICAN LIBRARY ASSOICIATION 50 East Huron Street, Chicaho, Illinois 60611 c1980 ALA'"
    - ALA "Video: An Alternative Information Service", June 1980. Part 2 of 2, 138.0163; 55205 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0163, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0163)
      Audiocassette, unmarked, 43 min.
      Preservation note: "All content has a background noise from separate content at an incorrect speed/pitch - the result sounds like a low animal growl throughout; Side 2: 00:00:00;xx-00:00:52;xx - O incorrect speed/pitch was unable to correct, removed for access copy"
    - ALA 1980 Annual Conference. Part 1 of 5, 138.0164; 55204 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0164, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0164)
      Audiocassette, unmarked, 93 min.
    - ALA 1980 Annual Conference. Part 2 of 5, 138.0165; 55203 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0165, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0165)
      Audiocassette, unmarked, 89 min.
    - ALA 1980 Annual Conference. Part 3 of 5, 138.0166; 55202 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0166, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0166)
    - ALA 1980 Annual Conference. Part 4 of 5, 138.0167; 55201 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0167, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0167)
      Audiocassette, unmarked, 91 min.
    - ALA 1980 Annual Conference. Part 5 of 5, 138.0168; 55200 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0168, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0168)
      Audiocassette, unmarked, 26 min.
    - Anthology Film Archives "Video Art History" May 10, 1984. Part 1 of 2, 138.0169; 55199 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0169, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0169)
      Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, 92 min.
    - Anthology Film Archives "Video Art History" May 10, 1984. Part 2 of 2, 138.0170; 55198 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0170, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0170)
      Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, 49 min.
      Preservation note: "Transfer OK (Side 2 is only 1 1/2 minutes long)"
    - Anthology Film Archives, Video Symposia III, participants include Bill Creston, David Cort, Les Levine, Nam June Paik, Paul Ryan, Ira Schneider, Aldo Tambellini. Moderated by Davidson Gigliotti, April 11, 1985. Part 1 of 3, 138.0171; 55197 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0171, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0171)
      Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 93 min.
    - Anthology Film Archives, Video Symposia III, participants include Bill Creston, David Cort, Les Levine, Nam June Paik, Paul Ryan, Ira Schneider, Aldo Tambellini. Moderated by Davidson Gigliotti, April 11, 1985. Part 2 of 3, 138.0172; 55196 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0172, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0172)
      Audiocassette, Sony CHF90, 45 min.
    - Anthology Film Archives, Video Symposia III, participants include Bill Creston, David Cort, Les Levine, Nam June Paik, Paul Ryan, Ira Schneider, Aldo Tambellini. Moderated by Davidson Gigliotti, April 11, 1985. Part 3 of 3, 138.0173; 55195 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0173, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0173)
      Audiocassette, Sony CHF90, 41 min.
      Preservation note: "Audio levels fluctuate; static pops heard throughout; Side 2 is blank"
    - Anthology Film Archives Guerrilla Television Symposium. Participants include Ben Levin, Bill Stevens, Susan Milano, John Reilly, Skip Blumberg. Moderated by Deirdre Boyle, November 14, 1985. Part 1 of 2, 138.0174; 55194 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0174, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0174)
      Audiocassette, Sony CHF90, 94 min.
    - Anthology Film Archives Guerrilla Television Symposium. Participants include Ben Levin, Bill Stevens, Susan Milano, John Reilly, Skip Blumberg. Moderated by Deirdre Boyle, November 14, 1985. Part 2 of 2, 138.0175; 55193 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0175, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0175)
      Audiocassette, TDK D30, 5 min.
      Preservation note: "Side 1 is only 5 minutes long; Side 2 is blank"
    - Community TV USA segment on Broadside TV., 1976; 138.0176; 55192 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0176, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0176)
      Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, 59 min.
    - KPFK Long Beach LBMA Show Jay Kugleman interview with Deirdre Boyle., 1986; 138.0177; 55191 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0177, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0177)
      Audiocassette, Maxell UR60, 59 min.
    - Low Power TV Discussion with Parry Teasdale et al, undated; 138.0178; 55190 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0178, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0178)
      Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 95 min.
    - National Public Radio "Morning Edition. Celeste Wesson interviews Deirdre Boyle about LBMA Documentary show, March 10, 1986, 138.0179; 55189 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0179, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0179)
      Audiocassette, TDK SA90, 37 min.
    - New School and MoMA "Documentary Video: Subject to Change" with Deirdre Boyle. Part 1 of 2, 1988; 138.018; 55188 (Box 14, Cassette 138.018, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.018)
      Audiocassette, TDK D90, 95 min.
    - New School and MoMA "Documentary Video: Subject to Change" with Deirdre Boyle. Part 2 of 2, 1988; 138.0181; 55187 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0181, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0181)
      Audiocassette, Maxell UR90, 94 min.
      Preservation Note: "Side 2: 00:23:07;xx - O-original content ends, new contant begins; overall audio quality lower on ide 2 than side 1"
    - Port Washington Library "Video at the Library" participants include Deirdre Boyle, Karen Ranucci and Edin Velez, April 6, 1992. Part 1 of 2, 138.0182; 55186 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0182, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0182)
      Audiocassette, 90min. unmarked, 95 min.
      Preservation Note: "During the Q and A the answers are barely audible"
    - Port Washington Library "Video at the Library" participants include Deirdre Boyle, Karen Ranucci and Edin Velez, April 6, 1992. Part 2 of 2, 138.0183; 55185 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0183, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0183)
      Audiocassette, 60min. unmarked, 63 min.
      Preservation Note: "Side 1: 00:28:30;xx - O-main content ends, previously recorded content continues; Side 2 - previously recorded content"
    - Port Washington Library "Video at the Library" participants include Deirdre Boyle and Skip Blumberg, April 10, 1992., 138.0184; 55184 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0184, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0184)
      Audiocassette, 90min. unmarked, 0 min.
      Preservation Note: "Dubbed" tape - virtually all of the content is inaudible due to technical error during dubbing process
    - Port Washington Library "Video at the Library" participants include Deirdre Boyle and Shalom Gorewitz, April 14, 1992, 138.0185; 55183 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0185, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0185)
      Audiocassette, 90min unmarked, 49 min.
      Preservation Note: "Audio problems (especially on side 2 volume is low)"
    - Port Washington Library "Video at the Library" participants include Deirdre Boyle and Staff, April 20, 1992., 138.0186; 55182 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0186, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0186)
      Audiocassette, 90min unmarked, 92 min.
    - Video South Conference "Community and Culture: How Video Creates New Perspectives.", 1977-1978; 138.0187; 55181 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0187, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0187)
      Audiocassette, TDK AD-C90, 71 min.
      Preservation Note: "Audio levels change abruptly throughout both sides of content. An attempt was made to boost the volume on the access copies during the lower passages, but some of the content is still difficult to discern."
    - Video South Conference "Where Do We Go From Here?", 1977-1978; 138.0188; 55180 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0188, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0188)
      Audiocassette, TDK AD-C90, 68 min.
  - Subseries C: Other Interviews [not Subject to Change], 55172
    - Side A: Karen Cooper, Hope Ryden, December 6, 19zz; Side B:Bill Greaves, December 8, 19zz, undated; 138.0189; 55178 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0189, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0189)
      Audiocassette, TDK D IECI Type I, 93 min.
      Preservation Note: "Side 1: O-All content obscured by electronic feedback except the final minute - which is all that was used for the access copy; Side 2: O-content also has electronic feedback throughout most of the running time, but the content remains intelligible."
    - Peter Forgacs, New School Class, March 16,1995., 138.0190; 55177 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0190, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0190)
      Audiocassette, TDK D90, 70 min.
    - Pare Lorentz at Pacific Film Archive. November 10, 1976, 138.0196; 55176 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0196, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0196)
      Audiocassette, Fuji DR-1, 63 min.
    - Side A:Bob Summers and Penee Bender; Side B: Gringo in Maanaland, September 22, 1995, 138.0191; 55175 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0191, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0191)
    - DeeDee Halleck, "Gringo in Maanaland," September 22, 1995., 138.0192; 55174 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0192, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0192)
      Audiocassette, TDK D90, 94 min.
      Preservation Note: "Audio level fluctuates - volume boost to selected portions of the access copy"
    - Fred Wiseman, January 28, 2000., 138.0193; 55173 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0193, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0193)
      Audiocassette, TDK D90, 86 min.
      Preservation Note: "Side 2: some dynamic range fluctuation early in the content"
  - Subseries D: Deirdre Boyle's Trip to Australia, 55164
    - Peter Gilles discusses Metro Television-Sydney, June 18, 1995., 138.0194; 55171 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0194, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0194)
      Audiocassette, TDK D90, 81 min.
      Preservation Note: "some dynamic range fluctuation early in the content"
    - Bruce Goldstein and Steven Sbarge discuss Film Australia Sydney, June 1995., 138.0196; 55170 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0195, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0195)
      Audiocassette, TDK D90, 83 min.
    - Bruce Moir, discusses Film Australia Sydney. June 1995., 138.0197; 55169 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0197, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0197)
    - Cathy Robinson discusses the Australian Film Commission. June 1995., 138.0198; 55168 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0198, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0198)
      Audiocassette, TDK D90, 71 min.
    - Greg Smith discusses NSW Film and TV office, Victoria Trede discusses Miramax and Kerrie McGovern discusses NSW. June 13, 1995., 138.0199; 55167 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0199, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0199)
    - Tait. June 23, 1995, 138.0200; 55166 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0200, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0200)
      Audiocassette, TDK D90, 79 min.
      Preservation Note: "Side 2: During first 30 seconds there is tape damage that lowers the audio quality"
    - Robin Wright discusses Film Victoria, Ruth Jones discusses Australian Film Institute and Deb Verhoeven discusses International Documentary Conference. June 21, 1995., 138.0201; 55165 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0201, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0201)
      Audiocassette, TDK D90, 65 min.
      Preservaton Note: "Side 2: during first 15 seconds there is slight tape damage which impacts the audio quality"
- Series VIII: Printed Materials, 55128
  Following is a list of the printed materials that have been kept with the Guerrilla TV Archive. To see a list of the printed materials that have been separated from the collection, and cataloged individually, see the Separated Material portion of this finding aid.
  Materials are organized into 3 subseries: Subseries A, Books, Studies and Reports; Subseries B, Periodicals; Subseries C, Hong Kong International Film Festival Materials.
  - Subseries A: Books, Studies and Reports, 55159
    - European Television Report [begins on p.5], undated; 55162 (Box 11, Folder 293)
    - Miscellaneous Authors. Bound articles., 1970-1984; 55161 (Box 11, Folder 292)
    - "Primary" articles., ca. 1992; 55160 (Box 11, Folder 294)
  - Subseries B: Periodicals and Newsletters, 55131
    - American Film Institute Education Newsletter 4:1, 5:1, 6:1., 1980-1982; 55158 (Box 11, Folder 295)
    - Art Com, #21, 1983; 55157 (Box 11, Folder 296)
    - Cineaste: America's Leading Magazine on the Art and Politics of the Cinema, 26:2., 2001; 55156 (Box 11, Folder 297)
    - CineVue: A Publication of Asian Cinevision. 3:1 [located in oversize box], 1988; 55155 (Box 11, Folder 298)
    - The CoEvolution Quarterly, Winter 1977-1978, 55154 (Box 11, Folder 299)
    - Community Television Review, January and October 1981, Winter 1982, Winter 1983., 1981-1983; 55153 (Box 11, Folder 300)
    - Community Video Report [became TeleVisions] 1:1-4, 2:1-2., 1973; 55152 (Box 11, Folder 301)
    - Current: For People in Public Telecommunications. 7:16 [located in oversize box], 1988; 55151 (Box 11, Folder 302)
    - CVRP Patch Panel: The Newsletter of the California Video Resource Project. 2:6, 1977; 55150 (Box 11, Folder 303)
    - The Dial, July 1981, 55149 (Box 11, Folder 304)
    - et cetera. A Journal devoted to the role of symbols in human behavior. June 1977, 55148 (Box 11, Folder 305)
    - Global Village Air Time: A Newsletter for Independent Producers and Broadcasters. 1:1-4, 1:6-10, ca. 1980; 55147 (Box 11, Folder 306)
    - Image Newsletter 5:13 and 6:6, 1983; 55146 (Box 11, Folder 307)
    - The Independent Gazette: Journal of Independent Film and Video Artists, 1:1 [located in oversize materials], 1976; 55145 (Box 11, Folder 308)
    - LBMAVIDEO Long Beach Museum of Art Video: Museum 1:3, 2:1-6, 3:1, 3:2, 1981-1983; 55144 (Box 11, Folder 309)
    - Performance, #3, 1972; 55143 (Box 11, Folder 310)
    - QuarterPoint: The Focal Point Media Center Newsletter, Fall 1983, 55142 (Box 11, Folder 311)
    - Scan: Chicago Editing Center. 3:5, 4:1-5, 6:1-2., 1980-1983; 55141 (Box 11, Folder 312)
    - Southwest Media Review. v.2, 1983; 55140 (Box 11, Folder 313)
    - Southwestern Alternate Media Project Newsletter. 1:1, 1978; 55139 (Box 11, Folder 314)
    - Synapse TeleCast (Syracuse University). March and June 1979. Two undated copies [one perhaps from July 1979 and the other December 1978?], ca. 1979; 55138 (Box 11, Folder 315)
    - Television Laboratory at WNET-13: Vision News, Winter 1977 [located in oversize box], 55137 (Box 11, Folder 316)
    - TV Magazine, Spring 1983, 55136 (Box 11, Folder 317)
    - University Film Study Center Newsletter, October 1975, 55135 (Box 11, Folder 318)
    - Video and the Arts, Winter 1986, 55134 (Box 11, Folder 319)
    - Video Guide [see oversize materials], ca. 1980; 55133 (Box 11, Folder 320)
    - Video Tools. 1:1 and no.2. [photocopies; see oversize], 1972-1973; 55132 (Box 11, Folder 321)
  - Subseries C: Hong Kong Cinema, 55129
    - Hong Kong Film Archive Programmes, 1999-2002; 55130 (Box 11, Folder 322)
- Oversize Materials: Series I, 55075
  These boxes contain oversized materials from Series I: Files, primarily posters, fliers and newspapers.
  - Alan and Susan Raymond, undated; 55127 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Tom Zafian, undated; 55126 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Washington Community Video Center, undated; 55125 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Southwest Alternate Media Project (SWAMP), undated; 55124 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Image Atlanta, undated; 55123 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - 7th annual Global Village Documentary Festival, 1981; 55122 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - 8th annual Global Village Documentary Festival, 1982; 55121 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - 11th annual Global Village Documentary Festival, 1985; 55120 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - 12th annual Global Village Documentary Festival, 1986; 55119 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Global Village, undated; 55118 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Anthology Film Archives, undated; 55117 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Athens Video Festival, 1979; 55116 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Athens Video Festival, 1982; 55115 (Box 16, Folder 32B)
  - Athens Video Festival, 1983; 55114 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - "Perspectives on Community Video" DCTV Festival, 1980; 55113 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - DCTV Community Video Festival, 1983; 55112 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - American Film Institute (AFI) National Video Festival, 1981; 55111 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - AFI National Video Festival, 1983; 55110 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA) Video Publicity, undated; 55109 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Whitney Video Publicity, undated; 55108 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Miscellaneous Video Exhibitions, undated; 55107 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - The Kitchen, Fliers and Publicity, undated; 55106 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Long Beach Museum Video Publicity, undated; 55105 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, H. Klein, undated; 55104 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Independent Documentary Fund (IDF) and TV Lab, undated; 55103 (Box 17, Folder 57)